Barbara B. Kennelly Papers
© 2004 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Legislation, 1981-1998
    - HR 4075 - Rapid Deployment Strike Force Act, 1994 (Box 12:, Folder 112)
    - HR 96 - Civil Rights - Equal Remedies Act of 1995 (Box 12:, Folder 113)
    - HR 97 - Rapid Deployment Strike Force Act, 1995 (Box 12:, Folder 114)
    - HR 1048 - Pension Reform Act of 1995 (Box 12:, Folder 115)
    - HR 612 - Equality For the Blind, 1997 (Box 12:, Folder 116)
    - HR 664 - Airplane Emergency Locator Act, 1997 (Box 12:, Folder 117)
    - HR 3895 - 21st Century Firearm Technology and Safety Act of 1998 (Box 12:, Folder 118)
- Series V: Subject Files, 1978-1998
  - Subseries A: Pre-Congressional Carreer, 1978-1981
    - 1836 Law, Research Materials, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 1)
    - Consumer Information Catalog, 1978-1987 (Box 13:, Folder 2)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 3)
  - Subseries B: 97th Congress, 1982
    - 1 District Press Kit, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture: Potatoes, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 5)
    - BBK Background, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 6)
    - Bills Sponsored by BBK as of 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 8)
    - Budget: Balanced Budget Amendment, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 9)
    - Colt Layoffs, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 10)
    - Crime, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 11)
    - Debate Transcripts 1982 Campaign (Box 13:, Folder 12)
    - Defense: Engine Competition, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 13)
    - Defense: Nuclear Freeze, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 14)
    - Disaster Relief, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 15)
    - Education, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 16)
    - Education: Student Loans, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 17)
    - Elderly - Supplemental Appropriations Veto, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 18)
    - Endorsements, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 19)
    - Energy, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 20)
    - Energy - Call for Reports on New England heating oil, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 21)
    - Environment: Ground Water, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 22)
    - Environment: Weekly Bulletin Feb 22, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 23)
    - Fall Campaign, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 24)
    - Food and Nutrition, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Affairs: El Salvador, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 26)
    - Foreign Affairs: Haig and Shultz, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 27)
    - Foreign Affairs: Japan, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 28)
    - Foreign Affairs: Poland, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 29)
    - Foreign Policy, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 30)
    - Hartford - HUD Announces Grants to Fair Housing Boards, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 31)
    - Hartford - HUD Grant for Rental Rehabilitation, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 32)
    - Herschel Klein, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 33)
    - Historic Places, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 34)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 35)
    - Israel i-American Relations, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 36)
    - Juvenile Justice Forum, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 37)
    - Media - Contacts - Info, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 38)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Israel i Lavi Jet Fighter Engine, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 39)
    - Public Works: Highways, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 40)
    - Public Works: Infrastructure, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 41)
    - Publication Services/Consumer Information Center, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 42)
    - Questionnaires for BBK, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 43)
    - Rally on El Salvador, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 44)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 45)
    - Tax Bill, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 46)
    - Taxes: Oil Import Fee, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 47)
    - Transportation - Connecticut, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 48)
    - Urban: Urban Decline, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 49)
    - Veterans, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 50)
    - Women: Equal Rights Amendment, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 51)
  - Subseries C: 98th Congress, 1983-1984
    - Mutual Fund Fact Book, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 52)
    - American Council of Polish Cultural Clubs - 35th Annual Convention - Keynote Address by Adele Wilzack, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 53)
    - Art Competition, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 54)
    - Arts Caucus, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 55)
    - Beirut Bombing, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 56)
    - Connecticut Bus Maintenance Facility, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 57)
    - Democratic Response to Reagan's Radio Remarks, 1983 June 11 (Box 13:, Folder 58)
    - Financial Disclosure Statement, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 59)
    - Herman P. Kopplemann Award, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 60)
    - House Administration: Select Committee on Children, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 61)
    - Housing and Urban Development - Field Reorganization, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 62)
    - Israel Trip Notes/Lebanon Update for CSPAN Show, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 63)
    - Israel Trip Summary, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 64)
    - Jet Engine Competition, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 65)
    - MX - Rally on Capitol Steps, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 66)
    - National Constructors Association Breakfast, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 67)
    - Natural Gas Study, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 68)
    - Oil Excise Tax, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 69)
    - Police Death Benefit Bill, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 70)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Air Force Engine Competition, 1983 (Box 13:, Folder 71)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Layoffs - BBK Statement, 1983 May (Box 13:, Folder 72)
    - Social Security - Support the Pepper Amendment, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 1)
    - Southern Connecticut State University - Commencement Address, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 2)
    - Soviet Jewry - H Con Res 63, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 3)
    - Surplus Food Distribution Act, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 4)
    - Tandem Trucks Ban, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 5)
    - Tax Seminar - Washington, D.C., 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 6)
    - United Rubber Workers Annual Legislative Conference, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 7)
    - Various Statements, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 8)
    - Ways and Means - Taxes - Subchapter M - HR 3529, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 9-10)
    - Zelda Blackman Testimonial, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Questionaire - Results, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 12)
    - Charter Oak Physician, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 13)
    - Charter Oak Square HUD Grant Awarded, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 14)
    - Child Welfare and Foster Care Hearing, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 15)
    - Connecticut Society of Enrolled Agents - Wallingford, CT, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 16)
    - Domestic Relations - Tax, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 17)
    - Eleanor Bonner / Letter to Chernenko, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 18)
    - Farrakhan, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 19)
    - Ferraro - Finances, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 20)
    - Hartford Fire Leasing, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 21)
    - Hate Crimes Bill, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 22)
    - Heating Oil, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 23)
    - Hueblin Incorporated - Puerto Rican redistilling program, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 24-25)
    - I-91 / I-84 Interchange, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 26)
    - Jewish Ledger - 55th Birthday, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 27)
    - Job Retraining Bill, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 28)
    - Lebanon - Statement for Removal of US Troops - DRAFT, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 29)
    - Life Insurance 1983-1984 (Box 14:, Folder 30-33)
    - Loctite / LOCPAC, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 34)
    - Museum Services Grants Awarded, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 35)
    - New England Congressional Caucus: Environmental Report, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 36)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Layoffs, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 37)
    - Pratt and Whitney - GAO Report, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 38)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Gains in 98th Congress, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 39)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Pratt / General Electric Engine Competition Announcement, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 40)
    - Retirement Equity Act - HR 4280, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 41)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 42)
    - Stinger Missile Bill, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 43)
    - Tax Bill, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 44)
    - Tax - Retired Lives Reserve, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 45)
    - Univeristy of Hartford - Commencement, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 46)
    - University of Hartford - Library Services, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 47)
    - Ways and Means European Trade Mission, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 48)
  - Subseries D: 99th Congress, 1985-1986
    - Aetna Insurance - Aetna Advanced Management Course - Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 1)
    - Aetna Insurance - Breakfast Seminar, Employee Benefits Division - Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 2)
    - Allyn Atheltic Club - Dinner Remarks - Polish National Home, Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 3)
    - American Association of University Women (AAUW) - Connecticut State Convention - Southbury, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 4)
    - American Conservation Corps - BBK Testimony to Subcommittee, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 5)
    - Anti-Apartheid Act - Floor Statement, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 6)
    - Antonoia Parker - Tribute, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 7)
    - APSA - Women and Taxes Talking Points, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 8)
    - Asylum Hill Survivors for Action - Q & A, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 9)
    - Berlin High School - Remarks - Berlin, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 10)
    - Bitburg, West Germany - Reagan Visit, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 11)
    - Black History Month, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 12)
    - Blacks: Economic Problems Persist, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 13)
    - BPW / USA, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 15)
    - Carlow College - Women, Policy, and Peace Seminar; Honors Colloquium - Pittsburgh, PA, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 16)
    - Catholic Conference - Statement Request, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 17)
    - Communicon II - Central Connecticut Chapter of Women In Communitcations Conference - Farmington, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 18)
    - Computer and Business Equipment Manufacturers Association (CBEMA) - Tax Reform - Washington, D.C., 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 19)
    - Congressional Caucus for Women's Issues, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 20)
    - Connecticut - 350th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 21)
    - CBIA - Board of Directors Meeting - "Grace Commission" - Pebble Beach, CA, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 22)
    - Connecticut Coalition on Public Education, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut Letter Carriers Convention, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 24)
    - Connecticut Parent Teachers Association - Annual Convention - Cromwell, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 25)
    - Connecticut Society of CPAs - Notes, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 26)
    - CWCREF - Women in Power Seminar - New Haven, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 27)
    - Connecticut Women's Life Underwriters Conference - Southington, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 28)
    - Constitutional Convention on Balenced Budget Ammendment, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 29)
    - CPTV/IRS Student Discussion - "Understanding Taxes" - Washington, D.C., 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 30)
    - DCASMA - Federal Women's Program Luncheon - East Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 31)
    - Democratic Caucus "Forums for the Future" Campus Outreach - Boston, MA, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 32)
    - Democratic Policy Commission, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 33)
    - Disabled American Veterans - 64th State Convention - Farmington, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 34)
    - Donald Regan - Women / Geneva Summit, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 35)
    - East Hartford Aircraft Credit Union - 50th Anniversary Celebration - East Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 36)
    - East Hartford Party Effectivness Workshop - Keynote Address - East Hartford, CT, Easter Seals Telethon, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 37)
    - Easter Seals Telethon, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 38)
    - Farmington River - BBK Testimony, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 39)
    - Forget-Me-Not Association - Candlelight Service Remarks - Manchester, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 40)
    - Foster Care Hearings, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 41)
    - Frost Publishing - Photo Request, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 42)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce - Questions of National Policy - Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 43)
    - Hadassah Myrtle Wreath Award, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 44)
    - Hamden Chamber of Commerce - Business Wizardry II Seminar - Hamden, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 45)
    - Hannon Hatch Veterans Post/Loyalty Day Parade - Distinguished Luncheon Remarks - West Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 46)
    - HART-Felt Award, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 47)
    - Hartford - 350th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 48)
    - Hartford - Budget Discussion, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 49)
    - Hartford - Historic Preservation Grant, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 50)
    - Hartford - Lead Paint Study, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 51)
    - Hartford College for Women - Commencement Address - Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 52)
    - Hartford Women's Network - "Whats Happening with Women" - Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 53)
    - Hate Crimes Statistics Act - HR 1171, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 54)
    - Health Insurance Availibility Act - HR 1770, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 55)
    - Helicopter Excise Tax - HR 3139, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 56)
    - Helicopter Excise Tax - HR 3139, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 57)
    - Historic Rehabilitation Tax Credit - Philadelphia Visit, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 58)
    - Holocaust Museum - Ground Breaking, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 59)
    - Home Heating Oil, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 60)
    - Housing and Urban Development Appropriations - HR 3038, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 61)
    - Interstate Cost Estimate (ICE), 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 62)
    - Interview - Cynthia Wolfson, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 63)
    - Interview - Lightman, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 64)
    - Interview - Political Profiles, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 65)
    - Interview - Richard Cohen, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 66)
    - Interview - WTIC - Graham-Rudman, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 67)
    - Interview - WTIC - Hunger, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 68)
    - John Cotter, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 69)
    - Knights of Columbus Dinner Honoring Archbishop John F. Whealon - Cromwell, CT, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 70)
    - Life Insurance, 1985 (Box 15:, Folder 71-73)
    - Manchester Community College - Commencement Address, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 1)
    - Mark Twain Exhibit, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 2)
    - Medicare and Medicaid Second Opinion Act, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 3)
    - Medicare Newsletter - "A Family Guide to Medicare" by BBK, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 4)
    - Memorial Day - Glastonbury, CT, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 5)
    - Mid-East, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 6)
    - Miller & Schroeder Forum - Tax Reform - Minneanapolis, MN, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 7)
    - Milner - Hartford Advocate, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 8)
    - National Conference of Black Mayors - "Tribute to Shirley Chisholm" - Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 9)
    - New England Electric / Hydro Quebec Transmission Project, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 10)
    - Newsletter - Summer, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 11)
    - Nicaragua - Contras, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 12)
    - Peace Corps - Family Night Tribute, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 13)
    - Pfizer - Central Research Facility Visit, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 14)
    - Pratt and Whitney, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 15)
    - Preventing Children Having Children, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 16)
    - Romanian Poets, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 17)
    - Section 809 - Deficit Reduction Act, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 18)
    - Small Business Conference, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 19)
    - Soviet Jewry - Simchat Torah Rally, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 20)
    - Soviet Union - Helsinki Resolution - HJ Res 363, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 21)
    - Soviet Union - Parcel Bill, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 22)
    - State of the Union, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 23)
    - Student Aid, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 24)
    - Tax - Markup, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 25)
    - Tax - First District Town Meetings, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 26)
    - Tax - Presidential Proposal - Talking Points (mp), 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 27)
    - Tax - Property Casualty, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 28-29)
    - Tax Newsletter, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 30)
    - Trade - Ball Bearing Industry, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 31)
    - Transportation - Newfield Avenue Bridge Project, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 32)
    - Univeristy of Hartford Student Aid Rally - BBK Letter, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 33)
    - University Club of Hartford - Remarks, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 34)
    - University of Hartford - Barney School of Business and Public Administration - Business Executive Luncheon - Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 35)
    - University of Hartford - Commencement, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 36)
    - Weaver High School - Social Studies Forum, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 37)
    - Webster Hill School Visit, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 38)
    - West Hartford Chamber of Commerce - Legislative Breakfast with BBK - West Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 39)
    - West Haven Veterans Administration Medical Center, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 40)
    - AARP-Elderly Issue-Tax Reform, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 41)
    - Arbitron Reports, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 42)
    - Asylum Hill Organizing Project (AHOP) - Annual Convention - Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 43)
    - Ball Bearing Industry - Report, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 44)
    - Bigelow Mills, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 45)
    - Bloomfield High School - Bloomfield, CT, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 46)
    - Budget, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 47)
    - CHFA Project, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 48)
    - Chile Demonstration, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 49)
    - College Visits - Mt. Holyoke, Smith, Wesleyan, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 50)
    - Columbus Day Celebration - Achievement Award - Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 51)
    - Community College Leadership Conference, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 52)
    - Community Volunteer Festival - East Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 53)
    - Comprehensive Test Ban, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 54)
    - Conard and Hall High Schools - Excellence Awards Ceremony - West Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 55)
    - Connecticut Business and Industry Association (CBIA), 1986 (Box 16:, Folder 56)
    - Connecticut Grants and Contracts, 1985-1986 (Box 16:, Folder 57-58)
    - Connecticut State Federation of Black Democratic Clubs - Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 1)
    - Consumer Federation of America (CFA) Endorsement, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 2)
    - Corporation for Independent Living, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 3)
    - Crabtree Warehouse, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 4)
    - Democracy Foundation / DLC Boston, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Leadership Council (DLC) - Conference, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 6)
    - Dexter Corporation Project, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 7)
    - Dual Resident Company, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 8)
    - East Windsor Rotary Club - Message to Students, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 9)
    - El Mercado Grant, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 10)
    - FCC - Minority Ownership, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 11)
    - Forget Me Not Association - POW/MIA Freedom Walk and Rally - Newington, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 12)
    - General Utilities Doctrine, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 13)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 14)
    - Greater Hartford Community College - Commencement Address, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 15)
    - Hartford Health Network (HHN), 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 16)
    - Hartford Woman - Tips From The Top, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 17)
    - International Personnel Mnagement Association - Graham/Rudman Speech - Glastonbury, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 18)
    - Japanese / American Trade Relations - Tokyo Trade Expansion Center Steering Committee, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 19)
    - Latin America Trip, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 20)
    - Launch to End Hunger, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 21)
    - Leadership Greater Hartford (LGH), 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 22)
    - Machine Tools, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 23)
    - National Association of Bank Women, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 24)
    - National Conference of Catholic Charities - Award Acceptance - Washington, D.C., 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 25)
    - National Trust For Historic Preservation - Award - Middletown, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 26)
    - Network - Philip A. Hart Award, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 27)
    - New England Community Health Institute - Cromwell, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 28)
    - New England Council - Gramm- Rudman, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 29)
    - New Horizons, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 30)
    - New RIC Bill, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 31)
    - Newsletter - Winter, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 32)
    - O'Neill, William, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 33)
    - PCB's - Nike Sites, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 34)
    - Property and Casualty Insurance Companies, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 35)
    - Questionnaire - Charlie Morse, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 36)
    - Questionnaire - Connecicut Telephone Workers, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 37)
    - Questionnaire - COPE, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 38)
    - Questionnaire - CQ, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 39)
    - Questionnaire - Full Employment Action Council, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 40)
    - Questionnaire - Hartford Courant, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 41)
    - Questionnaire - Imprint, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 42)
    - Questionnaire - League of Women Voters, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 43)
    - Questionnaire - Regional Shopper, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 44)
    - Reading is Fundamental, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 45)
    - RHAM High School - National Honor Society Induciton - Hebron, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 46)
    - Risk Pool Bill - HR 4742 - Hearing, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 47)
    - Sheehan - Notes From Session With Mike Sheehan, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 48)
    - South Africa - Reagan Speech, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 49)
    - Soviet Jewry - Divided Spouses, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 50)
    - Soviet Jewry - Emigration Policy, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 51)
    - Special Needs Adoption Conference - Keynote Address - Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 52)
    - St. Johns Church - Lenten Service, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 53)
    - St. Mary's College - Commencement - South Bend, IN, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 54)
    - State of Israel Bonds, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 55)
    - State of the Union, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 56)
    - Tax - Connecticut - Tax Expemt Bonds, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 57)
    - Tax - Don Evans - Freight Forwarders, 1985-1986 (Box 17:, Folder 58)
    - Terrorism - Special Congressional Committee, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 59)
    - Trade - Background for UAW Speech, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 60)
    - Trade Expansion Center - BBK on Steering Committee, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 61)
    - Transition Rules, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 62)
    - Transportation - Charter Oak Bridge, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 63)
    - Trinity College Young Democrats - Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 64)
    - UAW - CAP, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 65)
    - Washington-Jefferson Streets - Dedication Ceremony - Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 66)
    - Welfare Reform, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 67)
    - West Hartford Senior Center, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 68)
    - West Indian Social Club - 36th Anniversary Celebration - Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 69)
    - Womens Conference - Opening Remarks - Hartford, CT, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 70)
    - WPOP Radio Debate, 1986 (Box 17:, Folder 71)
  - Subseries E: 100th Congress, 1987-1988
    - Act for Better Child Care (ABC) Bill, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 72)
    - Advest - Tax Problem, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 73)
    - AIDS - Surgeon Generals Report {report, letters}, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 74)
    - At-Large Whip, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 75)
    - Book Publishers, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 76)
    - Capitol Commentaries, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 77)
    - Choate - Adlai E. Stevenson II Fellow - Lecture, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 78)
    - Cigna, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 79)
    - Citizenship Ceremony - Hartford, CT, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 80)
    - Colt Strike, 1986-1987 (Box 17:, Folder 81)
    - Congressional Charity Basketball Game, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 82)
    - Connecticut World Trade Center - Hartford, CT [Speech, Letters], 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 83)
    - Faculty Housing HR677, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 84-85)
    - Glasonbury Chamber of Commerce - Glastonbury, CT, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 1)
    - Hartford Housing Audit, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 2-3)
    - Hate Crimes Statisitcs Act - HR 993, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 4)
    - Helicopter - EMS Helicoptor Bill - HR 2310 - Airport and Airway Improvement, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 5)
    - Helicopter Excise Tax, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 6-7)